starting, so I don't see Mr. Watson.
Chief, would you say the first one tonight?
And far enough on you, it seemed like we have no shows.
It's a good act.
And good.
We're a practice.
That's right.
God, I thank you for this day.
I thank you for each person in this community.
I ask Father that you want to open this community and protect it.
I ask it to be in the decisions that are made tonight.
I thank you for this council and the leadership that we have.
I thank you most of all here, said Jesus Christ.
Amen.
Thank you.
And we'll do the plan to serve you, sir.
I plan to do the plan out of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it's saying one nation, under God, the individual, with liberty and justice for all.
Thank you, Chief.
I force public input and special personal appearances and on the arts, which could rest the
authority.
I'm five as a consent agenda staff, as a committee in the claims and minutes, I'm
six and seven for the consent agenda.
There are no questions on these items.
They're kind of motion.
Thank you.
The war policy.
Johnson.
Lewis.
Hi.
Weston.
Forster.
Shots.
Hi.
New business.
New one.
Okay.
Staff reports.
We're in your packet.
If available, staff is present for questions, any questions for staff or anything, trustee
community announcements, any announcements.
I know there was a great, I was not here, but I'm not even a war dog, but I know there was a great
war dog event this weekend.
I was going to bring that up over to the United States of America.
Okay.
Well, then we'll take that up later.
Item 11 is a journey that we have a motion to adjourn the special utility authority meeting.
Oh, make the motion.
And a second.
Also.